[objects rustling and clattering]
[woman] Huh? What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Where's the rest of it?
[intriguing music playing]
[exhales]
[sighs]
Not here. Shit.
Fujita!
[Fujita] Yeah?
[woman] 21,500 yen.
- [Fujita] What? - [woman] It's gone.
Where'd you put the money?
Hey, don't worry. It was a
- An investment. - What?
- Don't tell me it's gone? - Kaho
I
I think I found something way better than a few thousand yen.
[Kaho] Hmm?
A collection of music videos from an idol group.
Underground, unknown, called Dream Succubus.
TAX INCLUDED PRICE ¥21,500
[Kaho] Are you serious?
You took the money for this?
The plan was to save up and buy a new camera!
[coins rattling in tin]
- Mm-hmm. - [Kaho sighs]
- Trust me. You'll wanna see this. - [Kaho] What? Why?
[Fujita chuckles] Come on.
[Kaho] I'm gonna straight-up murder you.
They'll execute me for it, like Dancer in the Dark.
[Fujita chuckles]
DREAM SUCCUBUS
[pop music playing over speakers]
[Kaho scoffs]
Oof.
I guess I gotta ask,
Are you, like, into this kinda stuff now or you--
It's not like that.
This music video was directed by Goro.
I like his work, so I bought it, and then
- Ah. - [music pauses]
Right there. There.
Wait. Hey. No.
- Look. - [Kaho] What?
[Fujita] Look. There.
[hopeful string music playing]
[Kaho] Wait. Is that
Great day for believers.
Kaho
We found it after searching for so long.
We're one step closer to finding the Human Vapor.
What no one's ever done before.
[music becomes mysterious]
The Human Vapor.
It's gotta be.
[Fujita singing]
[Kaho grunts]
[Kaho] No, no, come on, look up.
- Stop that. I'll take your eye out. - [Fujita singing]
- We've gotta start. C'mon. Go. - No, I'm not done.
It's already nine o'clock. We go live in five. My fans are waiting.
Four, three, two
LIVE
Welcome to horror paradise!
Hi! We're back again with Fujita and Kaho's Terror Zone.
- I'm Fujita. - [Kaho] And I'm Kaho!
How are you killers tonight?
You ready to be terrified?
Of course you are, right?
Because you all know what we're about to share
is guaranteed to mess you up.
Our videos will have you shaking in your boots!
Huh?
Or whatever shoes you've got on!
[Kaho] Drop the footwear and get to the point!
Go on, quick. The main event.
Main event.
Tonight.
Now I bet you know what we're talking about.
It's everywhere you look.
Let me hear you say it
[curious music playing]
You're so right.
The Human Vapor.
[chuckles softly]
[Fujita] Enough theatrics! You saw the announcement.
Now you're here for the goods, super rare footage that will reveal,
Once and for all, the true identity of the Human Vapor,
Here on Fujita and Kaho's Terror Zone!
[yells excitedly]
Oh, I hope you're ready for the scare of your life!
Kaho roll it!
[dramatic drumbeats]
[pop music playing]
- I don't get it. - [Kaho sighs]
- I'm serious. It doesn't make sense. - [Kaho sighs]
I figured we'd crack at least 100 viewers.
[Kaho chuckles]
Seven isn't quite 100, you're right.
[chuckles] So what do we do now?
[Kaho chuckles]
Here, close your eyes.
[Fujita sighs] Come on.
- Close your eyes. - Okay.
- Kaho, maybe it's time for you to host-- - No, I already told you.
[gentle piano music playing]
It's just
You're just, like
You're way more beautiful than you think you are, Kaho.
Do you know that?
Ah, ah, ah! Ah!
Stop, that hurts!
So, hey
You know if this keeps up, there's no way we're gonna make it.
[both chuckle]
Ow, that stings, stop! Ah!
- [Kaho laughs] - Ow.
- Sorry. - [phone buzzes]
- Whoa, look at this. Right here. - [Kaho] Mm-hmm?
[Fujita] This is crazy, look.
[Kaho] What? Wait. Hey, hey. Look!
[Fujita] "@dadashow"
"I was very intrigued by today's video."
"I would like to purchase the details of your investigation."
What?
No way.
Is this real?
Uh, so should we
At least, like, hear the offer?
- Yeah. - Mm.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll [chuckles]
[Kaho sighs happily]
I'm gonna send them my phone number.
If whoever this is reaches out after that, then it's real.
[Fujita] Yo, Kaho. Take a look at this.
Isn't this crazy cool? [chuckles]
- That's been there forever. - Huh?
- Don't you remember? You found it. - What? When?
I don't know for sure, but
Mom was there.
- [Fujita] She was? Really? - Yeah.
[Kaho hums a tune]
[phone vibrating]
[Fujita] Is that
- Yeah. It's them. - [Fujita] They're calling?
They're calling, they're calling, they're calling!
Uh, hello?
Yes. This is Kaho from Fujita and Kaho's Terror Zone.
Are you are you "Dadashow?"
Uh-huh.
[scoffs] Well, of course, it's real, yes.
Yes, we looked into it.
The location of the building?
Uh
We can't release those details, sorry.
Well, that depends on how much.
Yeah.
Huh?
- Sorry, a million? - What? A million?
Uh Sure.
Uh
No. Uh, yes.
Right, of course.
Yeah. I understand, yes.
I do. No, no, no, that's completely fine.
Thank you, that's quite
Oh. They're gone.
[Fujita chuckles]
What did they say?
That they want it. For a million.
A million? You're serious?
- Yeah. - Like, for real?
- Yeah, for real. - Oh, it's happening! It's happening!
We're actually doing it!
- Great day for believers. - [Kaho laughs]
Great day for believers!
[Fujita chuckles]
What did I tell you?!
[Kaho] Dadashow.
[Fujita laughs]
[dark, dramatic music playing]
HUMAN VAPOR
There can't be a production company here. No way in hell.
Look, this is the best lead we've had to find this place.
If anyone knows, it'll be the company that made the video.
"In the Socks."
[gasps] There. Up there.
[whimsical string music playing]
- [girl 1] My mom's not home right now. - [girl 2] So we can do whatever we want.
[girl 1] Yeah!
We could get some snacks and play at the arcade!
[girl 2] Whoa. Did you see her face? That, like, bruise thing?
[music fades out]
[Kaho, over phone] Fujita?
Just be normal in there. Don't say anything weird or whatever.
[Fujita] Obviously. I know.
[Kaho] Okay. Step one, knock.
[meowing inside]
[meowing continues]
[meowing over phone]
What is that?
[meowing continues]
[man] No, no, no, that's all wrong. I need to see a cat, okay?
A real cat. A cat in heat. Like you're trying to attract
[Kaho] Go in!
[woman meowing]
[man] No, no, you're not listening! I need you to really embody the cat.
Hey! That's Cut. Cut! Cut, okay?
Imagine starting the meow like a siren. A warning.
- [woman 1] Okay. I'll try. - [man] Ready? And action.
[woman 1 meows]
- [woman 2] Excuse me, who are you? - Oh! Uh
Well, I'm, uh Uh
- [Fujita] Sorry, I - [Kaho] Say you have an interview.
- [Kaho] You saw the listing. - I saw the job listing on your
[Kaho] Website.
I came to be the director's apprentice.
[Kaho] I told you not to improvise.
- Do you have a resume? - [Fujita] I, uh
[woman 1 continues meowing]
[man] No. Cut!
RESUME FUJITA FUJIKAWA
[Fujita] My name is Fujita Fujikawa.
Mr. Goro, sir,
It's such an honor to meet you.
Can I just say
I am a huge fan of your work. All of your work.
You are imitating my fashion.
Who is this guy?
He's weird.
I'll do anything, sir.
- Do you know how to drive? - Yes.
Can you work a tailgate lift?
Of course, and I have my color certification.
Unnecessary.
Yesterday, what did you have for lunch?
[Fujita] A hamburger.
Your favorite ingredient to add to miso soup?
I don't really like it.
- You ever hit another person? - Never, sir.
How old when you stopped bathing with your mother?
I don't really remember my mother.
Languages you know?
Three, Mr. Goro.
- [Goro] What about German? - I speak some.
Then speak some.
Fujita, come on, do it. You have to.
[meowing realistically]
[continues meowing]
[stops meowing]
Right, you got this, buddy.
All this to say, uh,
I'm a big fan.
I love all your work, but, uh,
Especially your music videos.
There was one you did for Dream Succubus.
- Wagamama Nightmare. - Wagamama Nightmare.
You shot it in a warehouse.
It blew me away.
[chuckles awkwardly]
[knocking at door]
Sorry to interrupt.
[Goro] You should try it.
No one makes lemonade like she does.
[Kaho] What?
Wait a second. That doesn't look like lemonade.
What did she just give you?
[quirky percussive music playing]
[slurping]
[Fujita gulping]
How is it?
It's, um
It's orange juice?
[woman laughs]
What?
What the
So,
You passed the test.
In a world of lemonade sheep,
You saw the orange juice and told the truth.
Welcome aboard.
Those oranges come from my hometown in Ehime. I squeezed them myself.
With my bare hands.
[Goro] Isn't that marvelous?
The human body is truly beyond compare.
A machine can't deliver such exquisite taste.
The Wagamama Nightmare music video was filmed in an abandoned warehouse.
Where is it?
I've always been curious, sir.
Oh, well,
The band's manager found it for us. His name is Kenta.
Where is he now? Is he still working as a manager?
[Goro] I don't know where he is.
He said something about wanting to be an actor.
I wouldn't put it past him. He's a slippery one.
[intriguing music playing]
[Kaho] Hey, Fujita.
- That's Mimi. - What?
[Kaho] Mimi. She's part of Dream Succubus.
Maybe she can tell us.
Sorry, are you
Mimi from Dream Succubus?
Yeah.
Maybe you know something about what might've happened to Kenta?
No. I have no clue.
Yo, there. Look!
KENTA SUMERAGI
[Kaho] There he is. I knew it.
Yeah, good call.
[music fades out]
[Fujita] Come on, Kaho, let's get you in there. Come on. Move.
- [Kaho] No, I told you. - It's your turn.
[Kaho] You go in. Like you did with Goro.
No way! You know it would be weird for a guy to go in there alone.
Wear a disguise then, I don't know.
[Fujita sighs]
Kaho.
Think of the money. Think about that.
We see Kenta, find out where the building is,
And we earn a million!
Yeah, I know, it's just that I
I don't want anyone to see how I look.
[sighs]
That's fine, yep!
You just wanna go the rest of your life only talking to me, only eating with me,
And avoiding the rest of the world.
It's not like that. It's not like I chose this stupid face.
- Go to hell! - I know you didn't choose it! I know that!
But you can't keep hiding from the world and being sad about it forever!
- Now, get in there! - What do you know? Leave me alone!
No! Stop!
Open the door! Hey!
Ah, come on Hey!
- [banging on door] - Kaho! Kaho? Please.
Is that what you wanna hear? I'm begging you!
Okay? Could you please do it? Could you please?
Open up!
[upbeat dance music playing inside]
FUJITA FUJIKAWA
Ah, welcome!
[upbeat dance music continues]
[lively chatter and cheering inside]
- Is is Kenta free? - Kenta's with someone at the moment.
In the meantime, we can offer you a table so you can wait for him, if you'd like?
Okay, sure.
Great! Right this way.
We have a customer coming in.
[hosts] Welcome!
[Fujita] Kaho.
Kaho?
Can you hear me?
If you can hear me, say something. Are you okay in there?
Wait, was that Mimi?
That was Mimi!
That was Mimi, wasn't it?
Kaho?
[host] Here you are. It'll just be a moment.
[Fujita] Can you hear me? Are you okay?
[quietly] Yeah, it's cool. I'll figure something out.
I can confirm that Kenta is on the other side of the room.
[Fujita] Seriously? Call him over!
[man] It's okay, don't worry.
[Mimi laughs]
- [man 2] Another round! - [people cheering]
- [people chanting] - [cork pops]
[chanting]
[dream-like music playing]
- [hosts] Drink it down, keep it up! - [people laughing]
[indistinct chattering]
[hosts] Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
- [host 1] A round of applause! - [woman 1] Hell, yeah!
- [host 2] Whoa, hang on. You okay? - [woman 2 laughs] You hang on!
- [dream-like music continues] - [indistinct chatter and laughing]
[man] Excuse me.
- Excuse me, miss? - [music fades]
I'd like to make this a night to remember.
How does that sound to you?
Pleasure to meet you. My name's Kenta.
Welcome to my world.
[soft, quirky music playing]
KENTA SUMERAGI
May I sit with you?
Nice and easy. Don't ask anything that could give away the game.
Just set the mood.
Uh, so, uh
I I don't
- It's dark in here. - Yeah. Sorry?
Why don't I take those off?
- No, no. - [Kenta] Hey, it's okay.
Sh, sh.
[Kaho] No, I just
[Kenta] Sh, sh, sh, sh.
[shushing softly]
[Kaho whimpers softly]
[Kaho groans]
You have such beautiful eyes.
Why would you hide them?
Careful now.
That's just him trying to butter you up.
Cheers then, miss!
[glasses clink]
Kaho, that's alcohol.
Probably strong.
Slow down. It's alcoholic.
Don't drink the whole thing. Just
[Fujita sighs]
- [Kaho] Mm. - [Kenta chuckles]
Whoa. Nice. You want another?
Yeah.
[clicks fingers]
[Kaho chuckles]
[Kenta clicks tongue]
- [Kaho giggles] - [clicks tongue]
Kaho, you okay?
The mood's probably good now. Let's ask him.
- For you. - Uh, thanks. [chuckles]
Yeah, thanks.
- I'll take another glass, actually. - Of course.
[Fujita] You've had enough. You don't need any more.
Yeah, I know! Shush!
Hmm? What was that?
Oh, uh
- It was nothing. - Hmm.
I can't figure out why you'd wanna know where that abandoned building is.
- You shooting a movie? - No, a movie?
- [Kaho] I mean Kinda. - Wait. Yeah, yeah, okay.
We've got big plans to shoot a horror movie.
[Kaho] Yeah, we've got
Really big plans to film a horror movie.
[Fujita] In the movie, there's an idol
There's an idol who comes back from the dead as a vengeful spirit.
- Kills other idols - And then she, like
Uh She kills people, she kills more popular idols, one by one.
Uh, hey,
Do you, like, need more actors?
It's just that the whole reason I got into this in the first place
Was to be an actor.
- I work here for now, but - [Fujita] Manager.
- Well - We're looking for a manager.
We do need a new manager.
Like, someone to play him. The manager.
- I think you'd be perfect for it. - You think so? Really?
The movie opens on a wide shot of the abandoned warehouse.
And then, a ways away, we see her
The ghost of the dead idol.
The new girl group is coming.
They're shooting a music video at the warehouse,
And they don't notice anything out of the ordinary.
Until our girl group's manager,
Who was just helping out on set, all of a sudden
All of a sudden, he feels a damp, clammy, cold hand--
Wait, wait, stop.
You said it opened on the group arriving at the warehouse?
- Then - [Kaho] Hmm?
Nobody quite knew why, but that day, there was a chill in the air
[eerie music playing]
[Kenta] There's an old abandoned factory in Katsushika. I think it's still there.
It's funny, ever since I was a kid, people had talked about it being haunted,
so I always stayed away. Until that day.
[Kenta] Okay, ladies, we're here. Everyone out.
Hey! We might have to leave. Keep the van running.
- Tenga! - Sir?
If anyone asks, you tell them you're with the Tokyo Film School.
- You hear me? - [Tenga] Yes, Mr. Goro.
[Kenta] It was the perfect location for the shoot, so I recommended we use it.
[wind whistling]
[Kenta] It's hard to put into words, honestly,
but there was something about that place.
Something wrong.
And then, we were just about to start shooting at the back of the lot
There.
Hey, I got that.
Uh, Kenta
I don't wanna be here. I'm scared.
Can you give me a hug?
- No, I can't give you a hug here. - Why not?
I'm really scared.
[Kenta grunts]
[Mimi laughs]
Anna.
You know I don't like waiting.
Mimi, pull yourself together.
You know idols aren't allowed to date.
And action, action!
These six devils will haunt your dreams tonight!
- Miho! - Mai!
- Mimi! - Ayaka!
- Yuri! - Anna!
[together] Dream Succubus!
[music starts]
[gothic pop music playing]
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Wagamama nightmare ♪
♪ Dream Succubus ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
What? What's the matter?
You forgot the choreography. Again! Kenta!
- On it! - [Goro] First positions! Starting again!
[sighs] What's wrong?
- Kenta. - Yeah?
Look.
[eerie, suspenseful music playing]
What are you looking at? Is there something there?
No. It's nothing.
[Goro] Good. Back to one! I wanna get this in one take!
[woman] Places, everyone! Let's go!
[Kenta] It wasn't nothing. I saw it too.
But I explained it away at the time. Thought I was just imagining things.
But then I saw the finished music video, and I knew
[Mimi laughs]
- [man] Come on - Oh, Leo
- I love your skin. It's so pretty. - [Leo] Smooth, right?
- [Leo] I've got a new skincare routine. - Ah, you're cute!
- Look at you! - [Leo] Okay, hands off the face now.
[Leo] That's enough!
[Kenta sighs] We all had a lot of fun before
Mm Mm-hmm.
[gags]
Whoa! Hey! You okay?
You okay? You gonna puke?
- You all right? - [slurps]
Yeah? Hey.
- [Kaho gulps] - You okay?
- Yeah, all good. - Right.
[Kaho gags]
- [gags] - Oh, whoa!
[Fujita] Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
[sighs] I told you not to drink so much.
You know how much that puke cost?
[Kaho] Please shut up.
[coughs] Whatever. We got the address, didn't we?
Once we tell Dadashow, we get paid.
- If they're telling the truth. - So it was worth it.
[Fujita] Katsushika Ward, Tateishi Kita--
- We're not going there now? - Obviously.
[Kaho] No! You can't make me!
- I wanna go home. - Get in the van.
- I wanna have a bath, I stink. - Trust me, I know.
- I'm tired. My head hurts. - Okay, got it.
- I don't feel good. Hmm. - Okay, directions.
As soon as we have the money,
You can get that treatment you always wanted.
[Fujita whistles]
[Kaho chuckles]
Okay. Thanks, bro.
Okay, well in that case
I guess I'll be on camera too.
What? For the live streams? You wanna host?
- You changed your mind? - Quit it.
- Awesome! - No. Hey!
- You're gonna host? Hell yeah! - [Kaho laughs]
- Great day for believers! - [Kaho groans]
Great day for believers!
- All right! - You're so loud. My head.
[Fujita] We're gonna have a million subscribers, baby!
[Kaho] Yo, could you-- I'm gonna puke. Slow down!
[haunting music playing]
This is the creepiest place.
Let's just get what we need and get outta here.
[Fujita] Hey! Kaho, check it out!
[Kaho] What? Where?
[haunting music continues]
[Fujita] Is that the window?
- [Kaho] Is it? Looks right to me. - [Fujita] No, not the one.
We're looking for a blue door.
[wind whistling]
Fujita, Fujita.
[Fujita] Uh?
Look, right there.
- That's the one. That's the blue door. - Yeah.
[Fujita gasps] Here it is.
[Kaho] Okay
[wind whistling]
[haunting music continues]
[breathing shakily]
- [clattering] - [Kaho] Let's not mess around.
[Fujita] We need to get more lights on.
- [Kaho] What? - [Fujita] J just find a light switch.
Wait, are you scared?
I've made peace with my fear, so
That's why I'm a true horror connoisseur.
[Kaho] What does that mean?
- [switch clicks] - [Fujita] Are you doing that?
- [Kaho] No. - What?
Who turned the lights on? What happened?
What if someone lives here?
There's no way.
Unless it's him?
The Human Vapor isn't going to pay the electric bill every month.
Right, yeah.
[Kaho] Whoa.
- Fujita! Look! - What?
- Down here. - What is it?
- [Kaho] Uh - [Fujita] Where do you think it goes?
[water dripping]
[eerie music playing]
Right.
Come on, let's go.
[Fujita grunting]
[eerie music continues]
- [Fujita] What is this place? - [Kaho grunts]
[Fujita] Whoa.
[door rattling]
What's over there?
[music fades out]
[yelps] There's something there! It's him!
[Kaho] What the hell?
- [Kaho] It's just a cat. - [Fujita] Oh.
[cat meows]
[breathing shakily]
[Kaho] What are you doing all the way down here?
[Fujita sniffs]
[water dripping]
[suspenseful music playing]
Fujita, look.
We can get through here.
Okay?
[Kaho grunting]
[Fujita grunting]
RECORDING
- I I think something's there. - [Fujita] What?
- Where? - Look, look, look, there.
[Kaho] Fujita?
What is it? Fujita?
- Kaho. - Yeah?
Look.
Hold this.
[suspenseful music building]
What?
The Human Vapor.
You think it's him?
It has to be. Look at it.
Just look
[Kaho] Why isn't he moving?
[Fujita] He must be asleep.
[Kaho] What do you mean, asleep?
Whoa
CALLING DADASHOW
[Kaho breathes deeply]
[wind whistling]
[automated voice] The customer you have dialed is not available
They're not answering.
- If you wish to leave a message - Leave a message then.
Hi, this is a message for Dadashow.
This is Kaho, from the Terror Zone.
I can tell you where the abandoned building is.
I even took some videos at the site, so
Call me back, please. The sooner the better.
- Thank-- - [phone ringing]
[phone ringing]
What? [grunts]
- [zipping] - What's going on?
- [Kaho] Uh - [Fujita] What's going on?
- [Kaho] There! - [Fujita] What? Stop it!
- [Kaho] W what's it doing? - [Fujita] What is this?
- [Kaho] Look! - [yelps]
- [Kaho] What? What are those? - [Fujita] Dominoes?
- [Kaho] Did someone set a trap? - [Fujita] Record player?
[Fujita] No, don't touch it!
- [Kaho] What do we do? - [Fujita] I don't know! Wait
- [Fujita] Is that music? - [record crackling]
- [Fujita] What? - [Kaho] Wait a second.
["Ellie My Love" by Southern All Stars playing]
[Kaho grunts]
[Fujita] Hide! We gotta hide!
- [Kaho] But where? - [Fujita] Down there!
[Kaho panting]
["Ellie My Love" continues playing]
[lyrics in Japanese]
Do you know what this song is?
- "Ellie My Love." - Who's Ellie?
[Fujita] It's a song by Southern All Stars.
I think it came out before you were born.
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
Greetings, listener.
Go right ahead
And make a wish.
[modem connecting tone]
["Ellie My Love" continues]
[Kaho gasps softly]
[automated voice] Your target is Saburo Otomo.
I just faxed you the details.
Kill him immediately.
- [whispers] What did he say? - He's gonna go kill a guy.
["Ellie My Love" continues]
♪ Ellie ♪
- ♪ My love ♪ - [door opening]
♪ So sweet ♪
[quietly] Fujita, no!
It's dangerous! Don't go.
No, stop! Don't!
You'll get yourself killed! Fujita!
- ♪ Ellie, my love ♪ - [song fades out]
[record player clicks]
[tense, sinister music playing]
[exhales] What the hell was that?
What just happened?
[Fujita] I think
That song that was just playing
Must be some sort of trigger.
Wait, so,
When this specific song is played he
He what? Turns into a human?
[Fujita] Exactly, and then
His orders print out over there,
And he carries them out.
So what you're saying is That's impossible.
I'm saying the Human Vapor is being mind controlled.
He's not
Acting of his own free will.
[Fujita grunting]
Hey, Fujita.
- Should we be telling someone? - [Fujita] Telling them what?
That the Human Vapor's got another target.
If we call the police now, we might be able to stop him killing again.
Stop him? No way. No, no, no, no. Hey, listen.
- Hey. We're not gonna call. - [Kaho] What?
We're gonna take it up a notch!
We need to get videos of the puppeteer controlling the Human Vapor.
Just think what that would be worth.
We could get way more than they promised at first.
- Isn't that kinda dangerous? - [Fujita] Ah, it'll be fine.
We go in, we get it done.
You and I, we're gonna get paid,
Show off our prize,
Then turn our backs on this town and leave it behind!
Gross, dude. [laughs]
[laughs] Bleh.
- [Kaho] I just - What?
I don't know, you make it sound like our lives are awful, but they're not.
[Fujita sighs]
That's your opinion, but I don't agree.
[cigarette lighter striking repeatedly]
Okay.
[newscaster] Shortly after 7:30,
police received reports of a car being attacked by the Human Vapor
We gotta get back to the factory now, beat him there.
Fujita, look.
[newscaster] According to the Metropolitan Police,
the victim was Mr. Saburo Otomo,
president of the Fujishiro Syndicate.
Mr. Otomo was rushed to a nearby hospital, but was pronounced dead on arrival.
- Receiving reports that the Human Vapor - Oh my God.
first attacked him at work.
He managed to escape in his car, but was pursued by the Human Vapor
[whooshing]
- Go, go, go! - [Kaho whimpers]
[dramatic music playing]
[Kaho grunting]
[Fujita] Hurry! Come on!
He's turning back into a statue.
[Fujita] Oh shit.
This is so crazy.
So, if someone is controlling him, why does he come all the way back here?
[Fujita grunts]
I bet this is like his respawn point, you know?
- "Respawn"? - It's a video game thing.
It's where he starts.
Maybe he's programmed to go back to that spot.
[clanging and footsteps]
[music builds then fades]
Uh?
Who's that?
[Fujita] It can't be a coincidence. It's gotta be the person controlling him.
[footsteps approaching]
- [Kaho] They're coming. - [Fujita] Quick! In here!
[Kaho] What are you doing?! Hey!
[tense music droning]
[phone vibrating]
[Fujita] Sh! Turn it off! Turn it off, quick!
[Kaho whimpers]
- [Kaho] It's Dadashow. - Who cares? Hang up!
[door clatters]
[phone continues vibrating]
[vibrating stops]
[woman] Kaho from Terror Zone. Here I am.
You said the sooner the better.
[intriguing music playing]
[music fades]
["Wagamama Nightmare" by Dream Succubus playing]
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Wagamama nightmare ♪
DREAM SUCCUBUS
♪ Dream Succubus ♪
♪ Wagamama nightmare ♪
[song continues in Japanese]
WALK QUIETLY IN THE HALLWAY
♪ Nightmare ♪
♪ Wagamama nightmare ♪
- ♪ Uh-huh ♪ - ♪ Dream Succubus ♪
- ♪ Wagamama nightmare ♪ - ♪ Ooh! ♪
♪ Dream Succubus ♪
♪ Wagamama nightmare ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Wagamama nightmare, ah-ah ♪
[men screaming]
WAGAMAMA NIGHTMARE
[all, distorted] These six devils will haunt your dreams tonight!
- Miho! - Mai!
- Mimi! - Ayaka!
- Yuri! - Anna!
[together] Dream Succubus!
[music ends]